So this is respected entrepreneur, Sean Carradine Sr.
He went to go fix his tenants, AC in St. Louis.
The tenant called the cops.
The cops came, they accosted him, they arrested him,
they put him in handcuffs.
All the while he's like, I own this property.
I have the phone records.
I have all the documents.
People are outside like, sir, sir, sir, let him go,
let him go.
They did not let him go until a sergeant came
half an hour later.
And then he started telling them like,
I am a respected black man in this community.
Like I was the first to graduate high school in my family.
Like I'm an entrepreneur.
You see, when it comes to the oppressor,
their version of who gets access to humanity
is not the same as others' versions.
Notice that the only black people or any people
that they give access to white supremacy,
which is their version of humanity,
are people who are willing to be violent,
people who are willing to enact disruptive acts
of oppression, discrimination, et cetera.
So like all this, like I went to college
and I'm an upstanding citizen, et cetera.
Like that doesn't have any value to them.
If anything, that might make you more of a proponent
against white supremacy to them.
Oh, leppity Negro.
Yeah.
So like all this time that we'd be thinking,
like if we just be respectable black people,
that they're going to accept us,
they're never going to accept us.
They don't even accept white people of their own
who do not act like them.
It's not even about race.
It's about what you're willing to do
to uphold white supremacy.